A Pop-Tart will rise.
Unfrosted is a comedy, history film directed by Jerry Seinfeld.
In a time when breakfast is ruled by milk and cereal, a fierce
corporate battle begins over a revolutionary new pastry.
Bob Cabana / Teen Ravioli, played by Jerry Seinfeld.
Donna Stankowski, played by Melissa McCarthy.
Edsel Kellogg III, played by Jim Gaffigan.
Thurl Ravenscroft, played by Hugh Grant.
Marjorie Post, played by Amy Schumer.
Rick Ludwin, played by Max Greenfield.
Unfrosted is a 2024 American comedy film directed by Jerry Seinfeld from a screenplay he
co-wrote with his writing team of Spike Feresten, Barry Marder, and Andy Robin.
Loosely based on the true story of the creation of Pop-Tarts toaster pastries, the film stars an ensemble cast
that includes Seinfeld, Melissa McCarthy, Jim Gaffigan, Max Greenfield, Hugh Grant, and Amy Schumer.
Seinfeld's feature directorial debut, he and Feresten also serve as producers of the film
alongside Beau Bauman, through their production company Columbus 81 Productions.
Unfrosted was released in the United States by Netflix on May 3,
2024, and received mixed reviews from critics.
It was nominated for a Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Television Movie, while Seinfeld won Worst
Actor and Schumer won Worst Supporting Actress at the 45th Golden Raspberry Awards.
The tone is lighthearted.